Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[pleasant alarm ringing]
[ringing continues]
JULY 9TH. SATURDAY
LEE NA-MI. LET'S GO!
[Na-mi groans]
[alarm continues]
[Na-mi sighs]
-[phone chiming]
-[keypad clicking]
[Na-mi yawns]
SEODAEMUN-GU
SUNNY
NEW PRODUCT PROMOTION DESIGN
SEND CLIENTS EMAILS ABOUT PRODUCTS
ORGANIZE INVENTORY
[Na-mi] Play a song for me. [groans]
HELLO
PIPIBAND
IT'S D-DAY
SO JEALOUS. I CAN'T GO
["Hello" by PiPiBand playing]
NA-MI. RESPOND
WHEN DOES SHE GET OFF WORK?
7:30! WHAT ARE WE EATING?
JONGNO PORK BELLY
[phone chimes]
#MINTCHOCOLATEJELLY #SUCCESS
CROWDED
CHANGCHEON-DONG OFFICE
[Na-mi] Good morning!
BLOCK 206
TWO SEATS
ALREADY BOOKED
[man on video] Office workers
who were about to begin a start-up…
[all] Hi!
MASSIT GONAAK
STRAWBERRY FLAVOR RELEASED!
GO ON A DIET WITH YUMMY FOOD?
THIS IS A NEW PRODUCT
[woman 1] I'm gonna get a salad.
You want one?
[woman 2] Oh. sure!
-["Hello" by PiPiBand continues playing]
-[phone vibrating]
LOAN OFFERS
BLOCK
-[man] Hello!
-[indistinct video game gunfire]
DAD
DON'T BE LATE FOR WORK TOMORROW
OK
KO JEONG-HUN MERCHANDISER
NAVER STORE
-[phone vibrating]
-Yes. hello. This is Massit Gonaak.
[devices beeping]
[woman] Bye!
[commentator] Here's the pitch…
-And it's a fly ball!
-[crowd cheering]
-IS IT NEGOTIABLE?
-1.000 WON DISCOUNT
-I'M A STUDENT. HALF-PRICE?
-SORRY
[device beeps]
[man on video]
So if you haven't subscribed yet…
-["Hello" continues playing]
-[man 1] All right. my favorite!
[chimes]
400K WON A MONTH
[man 2] My God. that's unbelievable!
[beeps]
[Na-mi] Hey!
-[camera clicking]
-[all] Cheers!
[indistinct chatter]
ONE PACKAGE HAS BEEN DELIVERED
[doorbell rings]
FIVE BFF'S ACCOUNT
SCAN YOUR FINGERPRINT
-[all exclaiming and laughing]
-[music distorting and winding down]
[woman] Come on. hey.
we should take it all together!
[Na-mi] Yeah. all right!
All right! Cool! Okay.
-[woman 1] Okay.
-[woman 2] Hey! Come close! Come close!
[Na-mi] One. two. three.
-[woman exclaiming]
-[camera clicks]
[sighs groggily]
-[brakes squeal]
-[doors hiss]
[Na-mi] Huh?
Oh! Hey! Wait!
[grunts] Please! Wait!
[doors hiss]
UNLOCKED
[intriguing music playing]
[intriguing music building]
[vibrating]
[reporter on TV] In this age
of living with COVID-19.
wearing masks became fully optional.
Korean society as a whole
is gradually getting back to normal.
Though it is not rare to see citizens
who are still choosing to wear masks
on public transportation.
In fact. it's common.
[citizen on TV] It still feels strange to
take the subway without having a mask on.
Kind of. like. unnerving.
And in other. similar crowded places…
[hissing]
LOCATION
THAILAND
#THAILANDLIFE #RAMYEON #CHAMNAMUL
POSTING
[phone vibrating]
[vibrating continues]
[vibrating loudly]
DROP-DEAD GORGEOUS
SPEAKER
[woman 1] Looks like
you had fun last night!
I saw your guys' Instagram.
You were going wild at the karaoke spot.
Lee Na-mi! Are you still asleep?
-[recorded female voice] Hello?
-[woman 1] Uh. hello? Is this Na-mi?
[female voice] I found this
on the bus yesterday.
[woman 1] Oh. okay. I see.
Yeah. so that's my friend's phone.
LEE NA-MI
Were you able to get in touch with her?
[female voice] No.
Should I leave it with the police?
[woman 1] Oh. um. hang on just a sec.
I'll talk it over with my friend
and then I'll get back to you.
-[lock chiming]
-[woman 1] Okay. I'll be in touch soon.
[sighs]
[panting]
[lock beeping]
[lock chiming]
[woman 1] Why is this package
all crumpled?
Lee Na-mi.
[sighs]
Mimi?
That girl. I swear.
You in the bathroom?
Oh!
Hey!
What the…
[sighs]
[keypad clicks and phone chimes]
[sinister music playing softly]
[exclaims softly]
[nervously] Na-mi.
Na-mi!
-Ahh!
-[loud thump]
-Oh. fuck! You fucking scared me!
-[Na-mi snoring]
[woman 1] Oh. fuck.
Hey!
LEE NA-MI
I LIVE ON JEJU ISLAND
SWEET LIFE OF NEWLYWEDS
[phone chimes]
(_nameeeda_):
_eeunjoooda_ TAGGED YOU IN A POST
IT'S NA-MI!
-[Na-mi groans] Everything hurts!
-Well. yeah. of course it does.
You slept outside.
How the hell did you get home?
[Na-mi] I don't know.
Well… I think I got on the bus.
Huh?
[anxiously] Where is it?
-[objects clatter]
-What's wrong?
-Is something missing?
-Yeah. my phone! Call it for me!
-[hyperventilating] Oh. shit!
-Okay. I'll call it. Wait.
-It's not in the bathroom? Of course not.
-God damn it! I cannot lose my phone!
[anxiously] Maybe outside? Oh. God. no!
-[camera clicking]
-[woman 1] Take a good look around.
LG TWINS
[phone vibrating]
DROP-DEAD GORGEOUS
[Na-mi] Uh. hello?
I'm the owner of the phone you found.
-[female voice] Hello.
-[Na-mi] Oh. thank you so much.
I was so tired yesterday.
I didn't even realize I lost it.
I took way too long to call you. didn't I?
[female voice] It's okay.
[Na-mi] Where are you right now?
If it's convenient. I can come there.
-[female voice] I'm in Seogyo-dong.
-[Na-mi] You're in Seogyo-dong?
If it's all right. there's a coffee shop
called Cafe Mizi there?
[female voice] Yes.
See you there in an hour.
[Na-mi] Okay. thank you.
INCORRECT PIN
PLEASE TRY AGAIN IN 30 SECONDS
[sighs deeply]
[mysterious music playing]
[dramatic note playing]
[camera clicking]
[insects chirping]
[officer 1 sighs] No prints.
no personal belongings.
UNDER INVESTIGATION
DO NOT ENTER
Whoever this bastard was.
he planned it out thoroughly.
Here. look.
Doesn't it look like
she was reaching out for help?
It rained all throughout last week.
I guess it was
so we'd find the body quickly.
God helped us.
Thanks to the rain.
all the evidence washed away too.
-And a boar found the body for us.
-Ugh. seriously?
[officer 3] Watch out.
-[officer 1] Did you find anything?
-Not much.
[sighs] But we did find this.
-[officer 1] What is it?
-Nutrients for trees.
-[officer 1] Nutrients for trees?
-Yeah.
But I'm not sure
if it's related to the case.
Could've been buried long before that.
[cicada buzzing]
[somber music playing]
[intriguing music playing]
[dramatic music playing]
WOO JUN-YEONG
[officer] A supplement that's the same
as this one was buried with the victim?
Then Jun-yeong must be the killer.
since that's his tree.
-Must be a coincidence.
-A coincidence?
With this much left. he must have
been there within the last month.
Same time as the victim's death.
Pretty conclusive evidence.
That kid kill someone? Really. Jeong-ho?
Well. that's what I'm saying.
A timid man like him
wouldn't kill someone.
So what is your theory then?
It's been seven years since he ran away
and he still hasn't filed
for separation of household.
Think he'd keep any decent friends around.
knowing that?
So. you believe
the killer is not him.
but one of the people he hangs out with?
That's right.
Then we just need to question him
on who that may be.
You know his number or not?
Jeez.
You haven't contacted him in seven years.
How can you find the guy?
Are you gonna get a warrant for that?
You gonna tell everyone
Jun-yeong's wanted
for being an accomplice in a murder?
For what?
Missing Person team's right here.
If you want to find him.
get a warrant first
and do an official search.
Yeah. let me report my son.
Woo Jun-yeong. missing officially.
[bell jingles]
[sighs] I'm early 'cause
I thought you might be exhausted. Dad.
-You're welcome.
-Yeah. right. [chuckling]
You find your cell?
How did you know?
#SHITFACED #LOSTPHONE
What? Ugh…
[father] At this rate.
you're really going to…
Ah. never mind.
Why give you advice
when you won't even listen to me?
So. when did you start Instagram?
What? I'm not supposed to?
Are you seeing someone?
Don't be ridiculous. Drink this.
You reek of booze when you talk.
[Na-mi scoffs]
[laughs]
There's fruit already?
I said call when you harvest.
[father] You said you were busy.
Your Highness.
-[phone ringing]
-When will you start moving the fruit?
[father] What do you mean. "moving them"?
No one wants them.
It's too much of a hassle. You drink 'em.
Yes. Mizi Cafe.
Uh. yes. Just a moment.
-Hey. it's about your phone. Answer it!
-Hmm? Mmm!
Hello? Yeah. hi?
[female voice] I'm sorry.
but I accidentally dropped the phone.
-The screen is broken.
-Sorry?
I left it at the repair shop.
I paid for the repair.
so all you have to do is pick it up.
-Well. you don't have to do that.
-Write this address down.
-Forty-six Jungang-ro. 103-gil.
-Oh!
Hyeongje Shopping Center. 414. Woo Repair.
JUNGANG-RO. 103BEON-GIL
HYEONGJE SHOPPING CENTER
[expectant music playing]
[pants]
[expectant music continues]
NO ENTRY WITHOUT A MASK
SMARTPHONE REPAIR AND PURCHASE
[tool clatters]
-[Na-mi] Uh. hello.
-[man] Hi.
I was told my phone was left here.
It's this one.
SMARTPHONE REPAIR REQUEST FORM
LEE NA-MI
BROKEN SCREEN
PASSWORD
[intriguing music playing]
NOW I'LL INSERT THE CAMERA LENS
PASSWORD
[dark music playing]
CHOOSE A TASK
[dark music continues]
INSTALL
WAIT UNTIL INSTALLATION IS COMPLETE
[sinister music playing]
[music fading]
[phone thuds]
[Na-mi] Oh!
Wow. you did a great job.
It feels brand new.
-Thank you. Have a great day.
-Bye.
[sighs]
[sinister music resumes]
HAVE YOU FOUND YOUR PHONE YET?
I HAVE!
DROP-DEAD GORGEOUS
-[Na-mi] Are you off?
-[woman 1] No. not yet. I'm on break.
[Na-mi] I found my phone!
Oh. wait. the bus is here. Hang on a sec.
-[woman 1] Yeah.
-[Na-mi] Hello.
[Na-mi on video] She left it
at the repair shop and even paid for it.
[woman 1 on video] Really?
That's super weird.
-Who is she?
-[Na-mi] I don't know. She just left.
Oh. right.
Hey. delete that picture. okay?
[woman 1 laughing] Hey. it's great. right?
Let that picture remind you
to be more careful next time.
[Na-mi] Shut up. I'm gonna get my revenge.
[woman 1] Yeah?
Want me to leak the pictures on my phone?
-Here you are. Thanks.
-[Na-mi on video] Forgive me. ma'am.
[laughs] Good luck
with your interview tomorrow.
I'll make you some plumade.
[woman 1] Ooh. did your dad
make plum syrup?
[Na-mi] Yeah. but he said
there aren't a lot of plums.
so he's not selling them this year.
There's of course still enough for you.
so don't worry.
[woman 1] All right. then.
[sinister music playing]
[music fades]
-Mmm.
-[gun firing on video]
BATTERY POWER 15%
[Na-mi sighs]
[bell jingles]
Welcome! How are you?
[man] Hello.
Um…
Do you happen to have any plumade?
How'd you know about that?
It's not on the menu.
Oh. I enjoyed your plumade
last summer very much.
Are you out or do you have it anymore?
Uh…
I'll get it right now.
[gun firing on video]
-I appreciate it.
-Enjoy.
Thanks! But. uh. wait a minute.
Um…
So you're back
to selling that plumade now?
No. I'm not sure.
There's not much demand for it. so…
Could I request
to have it back on the menu? I mean…
Not many restaurants around here even
sell plumade like this anymore. you know?
Mm…
Let me talk to my boss about it
and see if we can make it happen.
[man] Yes. please. That'd be really great.
We actually grow the plums
ourselves at home.
[man] Ah. I see! No wonder it's so good.
[Na-mi] Thank you very much. Enjoy.
What was the holdup. Pa?
[father] You know that guy?
No. why?
Well. you two seemed pretty close.
He's just a regular.
Regular?
[Na-mi] There is demand for plumade.
Why do you say there isn't?
Why would I sell it though?
It's not for sale. I…
-I made it for you to drink!
-Well. sir. I'm clocking out.
-[father] Uh. what about dinner?
-[whispers] Bye. thank you.
[Jeong-ho] Why don't you just
ask your wife?
She must be in touch with him.
He left to avoid caring
for his sick mother. you know?
You really think she'd keep in touch
with a jerk like that?
Yeah. kinda.
[pensive music playing]
I'LL SEND YOU SOME CHAMNAMUL
-DO YOU STILL LIVE IN GAYANG-DONG?
-I MOVED TO HWAGOK-DONG
AGAIN? WHY DO YOU MOVE SO OFTEN?
I'LL SETTLE DOWN SOON. DON'T WORRY
WRITE DOWN MY ADDRESS
THAT JERK MIGHT SEE YOUR PHONE
I WROTE IT DOWN
I'LL SEND IT TO HWAGOK-DONG
THANKS. LOVE YOU. MOM
WOO JUN-YEONG
HWANGHAE 102
[slurping]
[dark music playing]
[keypad clicking]
DROP-DEAD GORGEOUS
SO NERVOUS…
I MISS YOU. MIMI
DON'T BE SCARED
CRUSH THE INTERVIEW
[gasps softly]
[ominous music playing]
[menacing music playing]
JULY 11TH. MONDAY
LEE NA-MI. LET'S GO!
[phone alarm ringing]
[Na-mi yawns]
[man inhales deeply]
[sinister music playing]
ENTRANCE 93847462*
NO ROOMMATE. NO LANDLORD
33-82. CHANGCHEON-DONG. ROOFTOP
[panting]
[Na-mi] Good morning.
TAKES SEODAEMUN BUS 05 AND LINE 2 SUBWAY
[panting heavily]
THE WAY I LIKE IT RECIPE - MIX IT UP #37
SPICY CHICKEN CANAPÉ
SPICY CHICKEN NOODLES + CANAPÉ
kirke_nm. RUNS A SECRET ACCOUNT
412 POSTS
310K FOLLOWERS. 112 FOLLOWING
MIX IT UP LIKE KIRKE
SPONSORED ADS NOT WANTED
THE WAY I LIKE IT RECIPE
COMPANY PRODUCTS EXPOSED ON THE ACCOUNT
I CAN ACCUSE HER
OF ADVERTISING PRODUCTS SECRETLY
[Na-mi on video] Checkout. please.
[register beeps]
BALANCE: 472.645 WON
-[Na-mi] Eun-mi. Chu-yeong! Hi!
-[Chu-yeong] Hi!
WORKS AT A KONJAC JELLY COMPANY.
"MASSIT GONAAK." THE ONLY FOUNDING MEMBER
-[Na-mi] Hi. how's it going?
-[Eun-mi] Good morning!
[Chu-yeong] Gosh. you're so early!
JOO YEO-JEONG (DIGITAL SHERIFF)
MIMI. IT'S BEEN A WHILE
HOW HAVE YOU BEEN?
I'VE GOT A NEW NUMBER
JOO YEO-JEONG AND JEONG EUN-JOO WERE CLOSE
(NO CONTACT FOR 2 YEARS)
[Na-mi chuckling]
BEEN LOOKING FOR A JOB
SORRY I DIDN'T KEEP IN TOUCH!
CONGRATS!
LET'S MEET SOON
SAVE
[sighs]
EUN-MI. JA-EUN. CHU-YEONG. SOO-JIN
THOSE WHO SHOULD BE CUT OFF
FATHER. DROP-DEAD GORGEOUS. BOSS
LEE NA-MI
[dark music playing]
WALLPAPER
CHOOSE A PIC
Na-mi?
I just heard from G Market
that they want to do their main event
next week with our products.
Really?
I'm feeling conflicted on whether…
we should do it or not?
-Heck yeah. we should do it!
-[laughing]
The way you called me in.
I thought something bad had happened.
All this is possible
due to your hard work. yeah?
Oh. you.
[exclaims] This is so good!
Congratulations. Ms. Oh.
Had to be difficult
working at a small company.
Thanks so much for hanging in
and not abandoning us.
[chuckles softly]
Speaking of which…
I want to discuss giving you a nice raise.
[breathes deeply]
Well.
I'm ready for it.
What is it. Ms. Oh?
We'll double it.
You'll double it?
[Ms. Oh] I should've
given you a raise sooner.
I'm sorry it took so long.
[both laughing]
Okay!
-Shall we tell everyone the news?
-Wait.
Your raise is between you and me.
Uh…
Just me then?
You have worked with us the longest.
This is how it should be.
Don't worry about the others.
So. then. if this upcoming event
goes really well. can the others also--
This is why I like you.
because you're loyal.
[pats]
-Well. okay then.
-Thank you so much.
Eat before it gets cold. And your pills.
So.
why are we having chamnamul suddenly?
I was reminded of Jun-yeong.
He used to love chamnamul.
Oh. really?
How has he been?
-How would I know?
-You don't talk?
What's all this about. huh?
Bringing up Jun-yeong?
I was at a crime scene yesterday
and I saw the plum tree.
We planted a plum tree for Arbor Day
when Jun-yeong was ten years old.
remember?
He said he wanted to plant it
where no one can find it.
So we went far into the mountains.
Where you could bury a body
and it would never be found.
I saw that plum tree yesterday.
Do you think maybe…
Where is Jun-yeong?
[phone vibrating]
-FIND OUT THE ADDRESS
-IS IT JUN-YEONG'S?
-YEAH
-FOUND HIM
[sighs]
[breath trembling]
-[Eun-mi] Oh. my God!
-[Chu-yeong] Really? That's so great!
-Yeah!
-[woman] We should take her picture!
-[Eun-mi] Congrats!
-[Na-mi] One. two. three.
[all] Jelly!
[camera clicks]
-[Ms. Oh on phone] Everyone ready?
-[Na-mi] Let's get started!
[machine whirring]
[Eun-mi] I'm exhausted.
Let's take a break real quick.
-[machine whines]
-[camera clicks]
[suspenseful music playing]
I WANT THE PIPIBAND CD
DO YOU WANT MORE PICS?
NO. I'LL BUY IT
WHERE SHOULD WE MEET?
[woman on PA] When using mobile devices
such as smartphones. please use earbuds.
whisper. and keep conversations short.
-[dark music playing]
-[money shuffling]
THE WITHDRAWAL HAS BEEN COMPLETED
GOODBYE
EUN MI-GYEONG
[dark music continues]
BUSINESS CARDS
WOO JI-MAN
[woman on PA] For the safety
of the passengers.
please refrain from using a smartphone
in between boarding…
-[Ji-man] He doesn't have a phone?
-[Jeong-ho] That's what I said.
This number belongs
to a woman named Eun Mi-gyeong.
Jun-yeong had it disconnected
two years ago in October.
And no record of a new number.
Man. this makes no sense.
What kind of person
lives without a phone these days?
46-13. HWAGOK-DONG. GANGSEO-GU
I was curious
if he was getting into trouble.
so I checked the records just to be sure.
He filed a lawsuit for fraud
in March 2019.
Fraud?
He was the one who got scammed?
Yeah. out of 25 million won.
And he doesn't have a phone.
but is in the phone repair business.
Do you want me to look into
the location of this place?
No. No need to push it.
Where are you going?
How are you gonna find him?
[car starting]
What are you gonna do?
I said what are you gonna do?
[intriguing music playing]
46-13. HWANGHAE RESIDENCE #102
HWAGOK-DONG. GANGSEO-GU
HWANGHAE RESIDENCE
[intriguing music continues]
HAPPY KEYS
[Ji-man] You're here
for the Hwanghae Residence?
[man] Yeah.
[footsteps approaching]
WOO JUN-YEONG
HWANGHAE 102
[sighs]
[dark music playing]
-[Ji-man sighs]
-[discordant note plays]
[exclaims softly]
[discordant note plays]
[laughs dryly]
[expectant music playing]
OH JUN-YEONG
NAEUM INVESTMENT
DAEHAN BROADCASTING STATION
PLASTIC SURGEON LEE WON-HAENG
EUN MI-GYEONG
WANTS TO GO TO THAILAND
EASY TO APPROACH AS A TRAVEL AGENT
RELATIONSHIPS: MOTHER.
JEONG MI-GYO. KIM MIN-JOO. CHOI SEONG-EUN
[phone vibrating]
IT'S BEEN A WHILE
FATHER
[sinister music playing]
[phone vibrates]
[phone vibrating]
[tense music playing]
[phone ringing faintly]
[phone ringing]
[ringing continues]
[keypad clicking]
THANK YOU FOR TIDYING UP MY PLACE
[father] Welcome.
How are you?
I'll have one plumade. please.
Uh. that item's not on the menu.
I had it yesterday.
Yesterday. my employee sold it.
but we usually don't.
So. today. I can't get it?
[chuckles] All right. you can order it.
-That's 5.000 won.
-Okay.
[cash register beeps]
-It's been a while.
-Oh. you remember.
I…
I'm good when it comes to people's faces.
And I only sold regulars my plumade.
so I always remember them.
Oh. okay.
Will you be drinking it here?
I'll take it to go.
[Na-mi sighs]
WE GET MORE WORK BUT GET PAID THE SAME
SOO-JIN
I'VE REACHED MY LIMIT
CHU-YEONG
SHE TAKES OUT A LOAN TO GIVE US MORE WORK?
-[sighs heavily]
-[phone chimes]
EUN-MI
WHAT IF THIS PROJECT FALLS THROUGH?
SOO-JIN
THE COMPANY WILL GO BANKRUPT. I GUESS
[keypad clicking]
WON'T WE GET A RAISE IF THIS GOES WELL?
I'LL WORK HARDER!
[exhales]
BUNGAEJANGTER
I'M AT THE CAFE. WHERE ARE YOU?
Hmm?
-It's Bungae.
-Oh. uh…
-[Na-mi] The Pipi… Pipiband?
-Oh. gosh.
Yeah. the Pipiband.
-[Na-mi] Hi! How are you?
-Yes! [laughs nervously]
-[Na-mi] Uh…
-Hey.
Aren't you the guy
that ordered the plumade yesterday?
You were wearing an LG Twins hat
and sat over there.
Ah! That was you yesterday!
-Yeah! Thanks a lot for the drink.
-Ah! Yeah.
[man] Wow. this is in great condition.
Um…
Thirty thousand won.
-Make sure it's the correct amount.
-Great. I appreciate it.
-[man] Yeah. Thanks. Great.
-Here. for the CD.
And. uh. if you don't mind.
can I ask you something real quick?
Uh. yeah.
Great! Uh…
Do you think these could
get resold at a secondhand store?
Oh. of course.
-[Na-mi] Are you selling these?
-Yeah.
Oh. well. couldn't…
Couldn't you just sell them to me then?
Oh. I don't see why not.
[laughs nervously] Okay! So then. uh. how…
How much money do you want for these?
Um. I'm not sure.
Why don't you just give me
my 30.000 won back?
-Are you sure?
-Yeah! Yeah.
-Oh. wow! Thank you. Here.
-And…
If there is…
any problem with the tickets.
please just contact me.
-Here's my business card.
-Thank you. I appreciate it.
OH JUN-YEONG
DIGITAL SHERIFF
[cup bangs]
-Here's that drink that you wanted.
-Yes. great! Thanks.
Sorry. you'll have to
take the to-go outside.
Uh. yeah. sure!
-Have fun at the game. okay?
-[Na-mi] Thank you! Enjoy the CD.
-[Jun-yeong] Cool! See you around.
-Okay. Have a good one.
APPLYING FOR THE REVIEW CREW
TAKING PART IN THE COMMENT EVENT
Thank you! Drive safe. okay?
-Lee Na-mi.
-Yeah?
You've been looking at your phone all day.
Oh. sorry. I was working.
Did you want to talk about something?
-Should I move to Seoul too?
-What?
But how?
If I sell the house.
I think I'll be able to get
a small apartment out here in the city.
Are you kidding me?
What. you want your dad
staying in that place alone?
Is this because of yesterday?
Don't worry about it!
It's not gonna happen again.
How can I not worry
when a weird guy keeps coming around?
Weird guy. who?
See? You don't even know who it is.
Earlier today.
[scoffs] What do you mean.
"coming around"? We were just trading.
Why would you take his card?
Why are you so clingy and stuff today?
Look. just think about it.
His first time there
and he posed as a regular.
Plus the CD and the baseball tickets.
-You think it's all some coincidence?
-If not. then what is it?
[scoffs] What more could it possibly be?
Just stay away from the guy.
-He seems like a creep.
-Why are you saying that?
I didn't even do anything with this guy.
I'm telling you to stay away
because you're getting too involved!
All right?
Do you carry that knife I gave you?
I would say it's creepier that you keep
an eye on me and are obsessed like this.
You know that?
-Get home safe.
-Hey. Lee Na-mi! I'm--
Ah. shit.
[suitcase rattling]
[sighs]
[phone chiming]
What the hell?
BATTERY POWER 15%
[banging on door]
Um. Papa?
Eun-joo?
-[banging on door]
-[gasps] Who's there?
-[lock keypad beeping]
-[handle rattling]
-[bang on door]
-[keypad beeping]
[beeping continues]
-[beeping continues]
-[banging on door]
[lock chiming]
[door opening]
[camera clicking]
Oh! So scared. [laughs]
[scoffs]
Jesus! What the fuck?
See? I told you.
You should install a deadbolt.
-[sighs]
-Is something wrong?
Come outside. I really need a drink.
[Na-mi sighs]
[Eun-joo] What the hell?
You're the one who told me to come over.
What?
I mentioned I fought with my mom.
I blew the interview.
and you told me to leave and come over.
Oh. yeah?
What?
Did you think I wouldn't really come?
[sighs] I have nowhere else to go.
I need you.
No. you just don't want me to yell.
Was the fight with your mom serious?
What'd she say to you?
Whoa! Orange seats? How'd you get these?
Got 'em from a regular at work.
Let's have a little bit of fun
for a change. hmm?
Ooh! They gave you
their business card too?
"Oh Jun-yeong." A man!
Ah… No. it isn't like that.
He said to let him know
if there's a problem with the tickets.
Problem. my ass. Hey.
Who is this boy? What does he look like?
Mmm. he has a neat look.
But he'd look better without glasses
and a nicer haircut.
-I think maybe you like him.
-What?
What are you…
[scoffing] Come on. please.
-You know what I'm talking about.
-Honestly?
I am pretty curious about him
because we're so similar.
You're already paying attention
to how similar you two are?
No. it's not like that.
I just kinda found out.
I've only seen him a couple of times.
So it's weird. you know?
And. I mean. even my dad
feels there's something off about him.
He wouldn't usually
say that without a reason.
[Na-mi] Right.
It says "Digital Sheriff."
Wait. why does this place
look so familiar?
[gasps]
[sputters] Didn't Yeo-jeong
say she got a job working here?
Ah! Let me check my texts.
Yeah. It's some kind of
digital security company.
-How do they work at the same place?
-I know. right? It's so weird.
-We can ask Yeo-jeong. I'll ask her now.
-[Na-mi] Yeah. ask her.
[dark music playing]
[exhales heavily]
[wistful music playing faintly]
[phone chimes]
DAUGHTER
SORRY ABOUT EARLIER
[chuckles softly]
CAN YOU DO ME A FAVOR?
[keypad clicking]
I KNEW IT. WHAT IS IT? - INSTALL THIS
UNKNOWN SOURCE
[dark music playing]
ALLOW ONCE - CANCEL
[keypad clicking]
ARE YOU SURE THIS IS VIRUS-FREE?
IT'S A PHONE-TRACKING PROGRAM
IN CASE I LOSE IT AGAIN
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
JUST INSTALL IT
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT TO DO TOMORROW
CONFIRM
INSTALLING
MOM RUNS SOONDAE GUKBAB RESTAURANT
DELICACY SOONDAE RESTAURANT
[woman] The guy who talked Mi-gyeong into
going to Thailand with him is your son?
I'M GOING TO THAILAND WITH HIM.
STARTING AGAIN. DON'T FIND ME
Can you tell me what he does for a living?
Can he support them both?
I believe he works
at some phone repair business.
Well. that's odd.
I remember Mi-gyeong told me
he travels overseas a lot for work.
I'm not sure.
I don't really. uh…
If he repairs phones. well…
then I think she must have met him
a few weeks before she quit.
She apparently had lost her phone.
But then she said that
someone told her they took it
to a repair store because they broke it.
-And they paid for it.
-Where is it?
-The repair store?
-[woman laughs]
Well. how would I know that?
[phone vibrating]
KIM JEONG-HO
MISSING PERSONS TEAM LEADER
[father on video] Aw. my poor girl!
You're so terrified of bugs!
-[mother] Don't cry.
-[father] Don't worry.
Your daddy will protect you forever!
-All right? Dad'll protect you.
-[father] I will.
-[mother] You're so lucky.
-[phone chimes]
ONE PACKAGE HAS BEEN DELIVERED
[suspicious music playing]
[dark music playing]
[father] Jesus!
Damn.
[grunting]
-[blow landing]
-[dark music building]
[tense music playing]
NA-MI'S DAD. FOLLOW
-[chuckles softly]
-[phone chimes]
eeunjoooda IS FOLLOWING
[phone vibrating]
[tense music building]
[menacing music playing]
-[officer] Come on. hurry!
-[indistinct clamoring]
[officer 1] Everyone. head up! Head up!
-[officer 2] Yes. sir!
-[clamoring continues]
Yeah. we're right behind you.
Hey. you! That's not it. you dipshit!
Get over here!
-[menacing music continues]
-[officer] What?
[menacing music fading]
[Na-mi sighs groggily]
[chuckling]
[camera clicking]
[Na-mi chuckling]
EUN-MI
ANSWER YOUR PHONE
MISSED CALLS
BOSS. CHU-YEONG
[gasps]
[mutters] What? What's wrong?
-[Na-mi] Uh. hey. call me a cab.
-A cab?
-[Na-mi] Yeah.
-A cab? Why? Why. what happened?
-Why didn't my alarm go off?
-It's 11:00 already? Oh. God. no!
-[Na-mi] Shit!
-[phone chimes]
Hey. I got one! I… It's 3827. Call me!
Sir. please… please hurry.
[man] Will do.
[tense music playing]
Huh?
YOU'RE MAD BECAUSE I GOT A RAISE?
I DO ALL THE WORK
I PROMOTED STUFF FOR FREE
YOU SHOULD BE THANKFUL
ARE YOU THIS KIRKE PERSON?
TAKE OUR PHOTO DOWN!
[tense music continues]
LAST PHOTO BEFORE QUITTING
I DID ALL THE WORK FROM THE START
AND SHE GIVES ME A PETTY RAISE
#RIDICULOUSCOMPANY #DONEWORKINGFORFREE
CHEAP-ASS INGREDIENTS
I MADE IT LOOK GOOD WITH PRETTY DESIGNS
A TEAM OF AMATEURS AND A MONEY-CRAZED CEO
[ominous music playing]
ROOTING FOR YOU
CAN I GET A REFUND?
SHE THOUGHT IT WAS HER PERSONAL ACCOUNT
KIRKE'S ID HAS BEEN REVEALED
[panting]
I think that I was hacked.
Ah!
Is that so?
I gathered your things
since you're quitting and all.
I'm sorry. I understand.
But it really wasn't me
who posted all that.
I'll file a report
to the police right now.
-If we find out who it was. I swear--
-[Chu-yeong] Save it. all right?
I honestly can't take this.
[Eun-mi] Hmm. Ms. Oh must be so upset.
She gave you a private raise
and got stabbed in the back in return.
[Ms. Oh] The main event deal
was called off.
Plus refund requests are now piling in.
You should've been more careful
with that "kirke" thing.
Ms. Oh. it really wasn't me.
I promise you.
You know me. Why would I ever do that?
Exactly.
That's what I'm curious about the most.
Why'd you do it?
I don't get it.
You don't believe me? Really?
If I do. what does that change now?
Ms. Oh…
Will this company rise up from its ashes?
I'll find who's responsible.
I will catch them and I will fix-- [gasps]
[menacing music playing]
SOO-JIN. CHU-YEONG. JA-EUN. EUN-MI
BOSS
[menacing music continues]
FATHER. DROP-DEAD GORGEOUS
[Eun-joo] Na-mi!
-[menacing music continues]
-[Eun-joo] Lee Na-mi!
What happened?
What are you doing out here?
You…
You didn't do it.
[stifles sob]
[sobbing]
-[continues sobbing]
-[Eun-joo] Don't cry.
DROP-DEAD GORGEOUS
-[continues sobbing]
-[Eun-joo] It's okay. It's okay.
SEOUL METROPOLITAN POLICE STATION
CYBER SECURITY!
[old man] It was my whole life's savings.
[young man] How could that fool you?
When have I ever asked you for money?
[Eun-joo] So what you're saying
is we have to bring some kind of proof?
Yes. come back with materials
similar to the ones written there.
Listen to me. please. sir.
we came here to ask you to find proof.
So whoever's responsible's caught.
Again. you need to have
proof that you've been hacked
in order to file the case.
A photo on her phone was uploaded
to her Instagram while she was asleep.
-She was hacked and that's concrete proof.
-But you don't have that proof anymore.
You deleted the picture off Instagram
and left the group chat.
Are you sure that you didn't post it?
Or that you didn't
get your account confused?
I'm telling you. I didn't do it.
[sighs] Right.
So organize the materials
on what you didn't post and come back.
Please. sir. we really don't--
[huffs] All right. fine. Let's go.
Wait. we can't just leave.
We gotta catch whoever did this.
[Na-mi sighs]
[Na-mi] Exactly.
-So let's go.
-Hey.
NA-MI - PHONE HAS BEEN HACKED
I NEED YOUR HELP
REALLY? I'M ON VACATION
I'M NOT IN KOREA
MY PHONE HAS BEEN HACKED
PLEASE IGNORE WEIRD MESSAGES
JEONG BO-RA LEFT
LEE DONG-GYOO LEFT
[groans]
[muffled grunting]
[muffled grunting continues]
FATHER
WE'RE TAKING THE DAY OFF
[inhales sharply]
[Jun-yeong] We're not
opening the coffee shop today.
I'll murder you… if you hurt Na-mi.
God. don't make me laugh.
I mean. it's how you treat her on a
daily basis that counts. don't you think?
There's no use pretending
to be a good dad at this point.
[grunts]
Actually. no.
I guess you are a fairly decent father.
There are dads out there
who don't ever reach out to their sons
when they've run away from home.
[dark music playing]
[inhales sharply and sighs]
It's because of people like them
that I'm doing this right now.
Hey. please. I beg you not to hurt Na-mi.
Oh. Na-mi?
She'll be okay for the time being
as long as she doesn't suspect people
for no reason like you did.
Don't even think of doing anything absurd.
[father grunts]
Do you know how many days it took me
to be standing over you like this
since I swiped Na-mi's cell?
Three days.
Only three.
There's absolutely nothing that I can't
find out as long as I have this.
If I have this phone.
I'll know what you bought.
and what you want.
and what you own.
what you've stuffed your fat face with.
who you like. who you don't like.
As long as I have this.
I can control anyone.
So what the hell do you mean by.
"Don't even think
of doing anything absurd"? Huh?
[dark music continues]
[Jun-yeong] Mm-hmm?
[laughs menacingly]
[alarm chiming]
[automated voice] The security alarm
has been deactivated.
[Na-mi] Isn't it kinda weird?
I mean. why would
the hacker do something like this
instead of taking my money?
[sighs] I know.
It's like they're trying
to screw you over.
Yeah. right.
And that means
someone I know is responsible.
You ever tell anyone. like.
besides me about the "kirke" account?
Why would I mention that?
You're the only one who knows.
And I didn't tell anyone. either.
Like. but I mean…
wasn't your CEO a little too hard on you?
How could she treat you that way?
-[sighs]
-[Na-mi] Well. yeah.
I mean. I get it.
'Cause it was all stuff
that only the two of us knew.
Stop it! Why are you
trying to see where she's coming from?
Regardless. we have
to find the hacker immediately.
I can't let it end this way.
Whoever it is.
as soon as I get my hands on the evidence.
they won't get away with it.
[sighs] Who the hell is it?
[jingles]
[exclaims softly]
[ominous music playing]
Do you know Yeo-jeong at all?
Um. she's just joined the company.
How do you know her?
-We knew her in junior high.
-Oh.
What a small world.
So in case you might have. like.
read into things here.
we contacted Yeo-jeong first.
but she had said she was on holiday.
and that's why we chose to call you.
-[laughs] I see.
-[Na-mi] Here's a plumade for you.
Ah. thanks very much.
Um…
So were you able to find anything?
Oh. I'm checking right now actually.
Did your battery perhaps
run out of power faster than usual?
Definitely. It ran out really quick.
Uh-huh.
There is spyware that's been installed.
What exactly is that?
Hmm. How should I explain this
so you could understand easily?
See this camera right here?
This becomes the eyes.
And the mic is the ears.
So if you look over here.
this right here is exactly what is exposed
to the person on the other side.
And location tracking is also possible.
as well as tapping calls. reading texts.
People can easily get their hands on these
for just a few dollars
on foreign websites.
So it's definitely a huge problem.
Uh. I haven't installed anything recently.
How did that spyware get on my phone?
I'm not sure.
Can you find out who installed it?
-Like. you know. backtrack it?
-[Na-mi] Mm-hmm.
I don't think that'd be very easy to do.
Why? 'Cause the spyware
you found on my cell is evidence.
Doesn't that mean
I can take it to the cops to file a case?
Yeah. even if your phone has the spyware.
that would mean your phone was
technically where the uploads occurred.
So proof that it wasn't actually you
who uploaded them is still needed.
And that's what's so hard about it.
Wow. this hacker is a meticulous one.
So. what now?
I can't just let them get away with this.
Well. for now I'll go on back
to the office and do some more work on it.
Okay. so is that it? Or…
No. It's just a start.
I cleaned your phone.
so you're able to continue using it
for the time being.
Oh. and. uh. also don't download
any kind of weird links or files. okay?
Right.
Then how should I pay you for today?
Ah. no. no. no.
You can just pay me all at once
when we're done here.
-Great. thank you.
-It's nothing.
-You don't have to walk me out.
-I really appreciate it.
Oh. I'm sorry. but could you tag along
to make sure the directions are clear?
-Oh. yeah.
-Wait. what?
Just use navigation on your phone.
I mean. there's nothing else
to discuss. right? That's everything.
It'll just take a second. 'kay?
[Eun-joo] What's with him?
-What's with you?
-What?
So. where are you headed?
Oh…
-Who are you living with right now?
-I. uh…
Because of the hacker.
Don't get the wrong idea.
So you're not
living with anyone right now?
[Na-mi] No.
Why do you ask?
I'm gonna be really upfront here with you.
The spyware that's on your phone…
There was no trace
of it being downloaded like you said.
What this means is someone installed it
directly on to your phone
without you knowing it.
And the purpose of this file itself
is to track your location
and listen in through the mic.
so it can't be remotely controlled.
I'm not following.
Well. it means that
someone got their hands on your phone
while you were asleep last night.
That's how they posted on your Instagram
and sent all those text messages.
Turned off your alarm.
silenced your phone.
Although…
you said that you're living alone.
So if I were to take an educated guess.
that would mean
someone snuck right into your house
and then ran away after doing all that.
[Eun-joo] What are they doing
all close together like that?
Are you sure
that it can't be remotely controlled?
Yeah. I'm positive.
[dramatic music playing]
[music fades]
[Eun-joo exclaims] Hey. look at this! Oh…
They found seven bodies in the mountains.
[gasps] Come on. read it!
You've been acting this way
for an hour already.
Yeah. well. it's been a long day.
I just need to be alone right now.
I'll call you later. Go on home. okay?
Is there something
you want to say to me? Or…
-No.
-What's going on?
Something's wrong. What is it?
You can be real with me.
Did something happen
when you went out there?
[softly] Did you do it?
What?
I know that it's ridiculous.
but we were the only ones
who had access
to my cellphone that evening.
You heard what he said.
There was spyware on your phone.
-Wait. are you saying I put that there?
-No. I'm not. but it kinda looks like it.
Is that what that man said?
That's why you're acting like this.
isn't it?
[exclaims softly]
That guy is an ass.
Why is he pointing at me
all of the sudden. you know?
Call him back. Na-mi.
-Tell him to come back here now!
-I need you to tell me it wasn't you.
And I'll believe it.
So then…
just say it wasn't you.
You…
You actually think that I did it?
My God. how could you.
of all people. question me?
All you have to do is say you didn't.
Why can't you just say you didn't?
Yeah.
I did it. all right?
I'm responsible for all this.
So what are you gonna do.
turn me in to the police?
Come on!
-Got any proof? Huh?
-You did this?
Don't you…
ever contact me.
[somber music playing]
[Eun-joo crying softly]
[menacing music playing]
[laughs]
-[crowd clamoring]
-[reporter] More and more bodies
are being found
on a mountain in Pocheon. Gyeonggi-do.
The police just revealed
through an on-site briefing
that because it is presumed
that there are more bodies
buried in the mountain
besides the seven
that have already been found.
they've decided that they will
continue on with the search indefinitely.
We have no way of knowing…
[chief] Jesus. what a joke.
You're all a fucking mess
without your team leader.
-When did you hear from him last?
-[officers] Sorry. sir.
[chief] Call him now! Tell Woo Ji-man
he better get his ass up here!
[officers] Yes. sir.
[Jeong-ho] All that up there.
Jun-yeong did all that?
And he killed Eun Mi-gyeong too?
[exclaims in disbelief]
Wait. are you sure?
I said. "Are you sure?"
Why didn't you say anything?
You should've immediately called
if you knew this was all him…
[mutters] Oh. God.
They won't just look past you going there.
they could pin all of this on you!
Let's erase the footage first.
We'll say that when you got there
it was already a mess.
and you just found the victim's phone
in the apartment.
It's all 'cause of me
that Jun-yeong is like this.
Pointing fingers
is not gonna help your case!
[bag rustling]
Here's Jun-yeong's repair shop.
Let's go there right now.
I don't believe any of this.
I'll have to see for myself.
So we're going.
[suspenseful music playing]
HYEONGJE SHOPPING CENTER
[suspenseful music continues]
[menacing music playing]
[Na-mi on video] Good. good! Looking good!
Do something else. Go.
[laughing]
[indistinct laughter on video]
-[Eun-joo] Wait. So I just do this?
-[indistinct laughter on video]
[Na-mi] Oh. nice! Yeah.
[Na-mi crying softly]
BATTERY POWER 1%
-[somber music playing]
-[continues crying]
[inhales sharply]
[Na-mi exclaims]
These couldn't be
his only patrons the past two years.
SMARTPHONE REPAIR
He only had
the people he targeted come here.
Eight forms. eight people.
EUN MI-GYEONG
There's one more.
-He could have gone over there.
-There's another victim?
-"Lee Na-mi"?
-[Ji-man] You look around too.
He must've dropped something.
[Jeong-ho] Dropped what?
Does this look like he dropped anything?
There's no info on this woman here.
Jun-yeong is just buying time!
[sighs]
Why don't we just take this to the media?
Yeah. if this gets on TV.
he might go into hiding.
but we could also save her.
I'm gonna catch Jun-yeong.
Back off. If you don't wanna help.
you're in my way.
And what if he murders her?
You know that's gonna be on your hands.
You all right with that?
-513 Sun. we're at Hyeongje--
-Hang on. wait. wait.
[chuckles] We're police too.
We're from Pocheon Station. okay?
Here. look. We're investigating.
Are you from the. uh. Gocheok precinct?
[officer] What are you doing
all the way here from Pocheon?
It's a classified investigation.
so I can't say.
So. the person who picked your phone up
left it here and also paid for the repair?
Yeah. That's when the spyware
got installed on my cell. I think.
-Your name is?
-Lee Na-mi.
From the way things look.
I'm pretty sure it was him.
"Woo Jun-yeong"?
BUSINESS LICENSE
He would have changed his last name.
Oh Jun-yeong.
What?
"Oh Jun-yeong"?
Wait.
If the Oh Jun-yeong I know
owns this place.
then the spyware
could still be on this phone.
I'll call his business.
May I use your phone?
DIGITAL SHERIFF
Hello?
Yes. I'm calling to ask a quick question.
Do you have an employee
named Oh Jun-yeong?
Oh. really?
Uh. hang on. wait a minute.
Joo Yeo-jeong. what about that?
[Jeong-ho] They're so strict over there!
[clears throat]
-[Na-mi] All right.
-[Jeong-ho] Uh. Lee Na-mi?
[Na-mi sighs] The nerve of this asshole.
[Jeong-ho] Uh. what's going on?
So. he pretended to repair my cell.
then he installed spyware
to mess up my life.
then pretended to help me.
What the hell is he trying to do?
-Well…
-He's not just an ordinary stalker. is he?
So what's he charged with?
What's this investigation about?
[scoffs] You won't say it.
but it's clear from the look on your face.
He films weird things for private
chat rooms like the Nth Room. right?
-So the fact of the matter is--
-Right. yeah. Correct.
That sick shithead.
-Where are you located?
-Near Sinchon.
-Live alone?
-Yes.
-He asked me that before too.
-He'll show up there for sure.
Let's go there.
And what if he disappears?
What if he never shows up again?
Then you're fortunate.
What?
Look. I don't think
you're aware of what's going on here.
Do you have any idea
what I'm going through right now?
My acquaintances all believe I'm crazy.
the guy I thought
was helping me out is an asshole.
and I called my best friend a liar.
[exclaims]
I can't trust anyone anymore.
It feels like someone's watching me
and listening in on everything.
And you expect me
to just wait until you catch him?
And what if you don't. huh?
Protect me from him indefinitely?
You can't. can you?
I just want to go back
to the way things were.
We need to catch him now.
We will. no matter what.
-So do as we say--
-I'll get him to come over.
[ominous music playing]
I'll get him to come over
to my apartment tonight.
[Jeong-ho] What? How?
[chimes]
[Na-mi] By using the spyware on him.
If I make him believe
I'm still oblivious to everything.
he'll show up there. I know he will.
Because that's his purpose.
If I keep it turned off.
he'll get suspicious.
And if he realizes I know everything.
he won't show up.
And if we don't catch him.
he'll do it to someone else eventually.
I know it.
We've gotta get him before that happens.
so I'll lure him to my place.
[phone vibrating]
[Ji-man] That's a solid idea.
Think you can do it?
I can do it. Yes.
[tense music playing]
I WAS A BIT SHAKEN EARLIER
ARE YOU FREE TONIGHT?
I AM. WHERE SHOULD WE MEET?
I WANT TO CHECK MY LAPTOP
CAN YOU COME TO MY PLACE?
YES. GIVE ME YOUR ADDRESS
[Jeong-ho] I've got
a bad feeling about this.
[Ji-man] Why? What's the problem?
She's confident 'cause she doesn't realize
who she's dealing with.
-If she did. would that change things?
-She should know the situation.
And what if we don't catch him?
We have to arrest the guy.
That's how we keep her safe.
[Na-mi on recording] He said let him know
if there's a problem with the tickets.
[Eun-joo] Who is this boy?
What does he look like?
[water running]
[Na-mi] He has a neat look.
But he'd look better without glasses
and a nicer haircut.
-[Eun-joo] I think maybe you like him.
-[Na-mi] What? Come on. please.
[tense music playing]
[chimes]
[tense music continues]
WHERE ARE YOU AT?
-[phone vibrating]
-[tense music building]
[car chimes]
[tense music fading]
I'M ALMOST THERE
[phone vibrates]
CALL ME WHEN YOU GET HERE
[Jeong-ho] What?
What?
That's Jun-yeong! That's him. isn't it?
[line ringing]
[vibrating]
OH JUN-YEONG
[vibrating continues]
-[dark music playing]
-[line ringing]
-Na-mi speaking.
-[line disconnects]
[dramatic music playing]
[Ji-man] Oh Jun-yeong.
[tense music playing]
[phone vibrating]
LEE NA-MI
[gun rattles]
[gun cocks]
Turn around.
Turn around…
shithead.
[tense music continues]
[suspenseful music playing]
Jun-yeong. don't move.
Jun-yeong?
That's not me.
Are you the cops?
Uh. yeah.
We just got a report
and we mistook you for the perp.
Well. that doesn't give you the right
to sneak up and pull your weapons on me.
Looks like we startled you. I'm sorry.
Although…
you don't seem fazed by the guns.
May I see some ID?
[automated voice] This number is currently
unavailable. please leave a message.
Why don't you
present your credentials first. huh?
Why? You don't trust me?
I sure would appreciate
having the names of the cops
who are out here threatening civilians.
You know what? Here. boys.
-You think you can do whatever?
-Hey. hey. No. stop. Wait.
-Hey. you can't just film us like that.
-I'm a civilian.
[Jeong-ho] Again. we apologize.
You're free to go now.
Man. something
about that jerk feels a bit…
He looks like Jun-yeong from behind.
[smacks lips]
Let's go to the car. Come on.
[phone vibrates]
[gasps softly]
[Na-mi] Excuse me.
[sighs] My phone is in my room.
We should be fine out here.
What happened?
Something came up.
He said he'd come on the weekend.
I called him but his phone was off.
[Ji-man] What's his problem
all of a sudden?
Maybe you tipped him off?
Me?
Maybe it's that the two of you
weren't hiding well enough.
I saw you both out there
moving around all obvious.
Uh. not accurate.
We saw someone suspicious out there.
I'll. uh. look up
the location of this number.
And once he turns his phone back on.
we'll get him.
But what if he's actually on to us?
[Ji-man] Don't worry about that.
This is the only place
that bastard will go. anyway.
Oh. Yeah.
But it's not like we can stay here
until the weekend. can we?
And with her phone situation.
she can't contact us.
-So what's the plan?
-[Na-mi] Oh.
I have an old phone.
I can just switch to that.
If I switch phones. that may frustrate him
into showing up here sooner.
[Ji-man] That could work.
Go switch.
[Na-mi sighs]
[phone vibrating]
[Jeong-ho] Hey. uh.
why would you talk to her like that?
[vibrating continues]
CHIEF
[chief angrily] Hey. Why is your number
on Eun Mi-gyeong's call records?
And why was the package your wife sent
found at a victim's house?
Is your son really the murderer?
Is that why you flooded the crime scene?
Is it?
-I was trying to catch him--
-Hurry and get back here. Where are you?
-I'm going to catch him.
-You crazy…
Major Crowley is this close
to putting a BOLO on you!
I'll help you. but hurry up
and get your ass back here! Fast!
-[phone chiming]
-[sighs]
[Jeong-ho] If we stay here
and Major Crowley finds out.
we won't be able to do anything.
Let's just go clear everything up
and then come back.
You're the only one
who knows about Lee Na-mi.
So. let's just go back.
Okay?
[Ji-man grunts]
[door opens]
-[lock beeps]
-You switch phones?
[Na-mi] Yeah. I just did it.
Hey. so. Na-mi. we're. um.
gonna have to head on back to the station.
Oh. that's all right. I'll be fine now.
You'll be okay on your own?
Yeah. I'm okay here.
It's not like this bastard's a murderer.
Oh. well. yeah. that's right.
Still. though. guys like him
are unpredictable. you know?
Uh. is there a safe place for you?
Like at a friend's apartment?
[wistful music playing softly]
[phone chimes]
NA-MI'S DAD HAS ACCEPTED
YOUR FOLLOW REQUEST
[wistful music continues]
NA-MI'S BECOMING A LOT LIKE YOU
I MISS THE TIMES WE SHARED TOGETHER
[Ji-man] If he contacts you.
don't go meeting him on your own.
Call us immediately.
Be careful.
That spyware could have been re-installed.
Don't download anything strange.
I'll stay in touch
whether something happens or not.
If you don't hear from me.
that means something happened.
Got it. guys?
I'll keep texting you.
-[lock chiming]
-[Jeong-ho] Text us.
-[device chimes]
-[bolt rattles]
-[door closes]
-[lock chimes]
Dad. are you crashed out?
[grunts]
NA-MI. WHERE ARE YOU?
WHAT DO YOUR CO-WORKERS SAY?
I'M ON MY WAY
WAIT THERE
I'M REALLY SORRY
[phone chimes]
OH JUN-YEONG
I SEE YOU GOT A DIFFERENT PHONE
ME TOO
CALL ME
He's not even trying to hide.
[keypad clicking]
I FELT UNEASY. SO I SWITCHED PHONES
WHY DO YOU WANT TO TALK TO ME?
[phone vibrating in distance]
[phone chimes]
YOU WILL BE CONNECTED
TO A REGULAR PHONE CALL
CONFIRM
-[chimes]
-[phone vibrating in distance]
[vibrating continues]
[vibrating loudly]
-[breath trembling]
-[vibrating continues]
[menacing music playing]
Papa!
[gasps]
[indistinct clattering]
-[keypad clicking]
-What?
[camera clicking]
[father muffled] Lee Na-mi?
Papa?
[father on recording] You've been
looking at your phone all day.
What. do you want your dad
staying in that place alone?
Hey. Papa?
[father] Look. just think about it.
His first time there
he posed as a regular.
Plus the CD and the baseball tickets.
You think it's all some coincidence?
[Na-mi on recording] If not.
then what is it?
[father] What more could it possibly be?
Just stay away from the guy.
-He seems like a creep.
-[Na-mi] Why are you saying that?
I didn't even do anything with this guy.
[father] I'm telling you to stay away
because you're getting too involved!
-Do you carry that knife I gave you?
-[menacing music playing]
[Na-mi] I would say it's creepy
that you keep an eye on me
-and are obsessed like this.
-[Na-mi gasps softly]
-[Na-mi] Get home safe.
-[father] Hey. Lee Na-mi! I'm--
-[menacing music building]
-[chuckles]
[phone vibrating]
MISSING PERSONS
CHOI WON-SEOK
Hey. headed back right now.
What are you talking about?
What?
[tires screeching]
[Na-mi] Where's my dad?
Tell me now…
before I kill you.
Do you want to find your dad
or do you want me dead?
Tell me where my father is.
Ah…
-[angrily] Where is he?
-Here.
[muffled grunting on video]
[Na-mi] Oh God.
[Jeong-ho] Jun-yeong. they found him.
They found him. but…
Found him but what? What's the matter?
Where's Woo Jun-yeong?
I was hoping to stay off the grid for now.
But you went and ruined all my plans.
How are you gonna make up for this?
I'll do anything.
Let my father go.
Oh. yeah?
All right.
Let's talk after you send a text
to Detective Woo Ji-man.
You said you would keep in touch.
[Ji-man] Where is that shit stain?
[officer on phone] According to procedure
of filing a missing persons report.
I registered your DNA.
And the results were that
you are very likely to be related
to an unclaimed body that was
found a year ago at the reservoir.
You should come to the station ASAP--
[Ji-man] You're saying
Woo Jun-yeong is dead? That's ridiculous!
[Jun-yeong] I'm going to bed now.
-I will be in touch tomorrow.
-[keypad clicking]
Send.
[phone chimes]
[paper crumpling]
Why are you doing all this to me?
What have I ever done to you?
Because I picked up your cell phone.
What?
-Well. you want some grand reason. or…
That dumb reason…
is why you're doing all this?
Why would you drop this precious thing
just anywhere in the first place?
So what are you gonna do now?
Well. now. the people around you
will decide that. starting right now.
If just one person
out of the many numbers you have here
contacts you in the next 24 hours.
I'll spare you.
but. Na-mi.
that has never happened so far.
I mean. in this world. we're all connected
by the twitch of a finger.
but that also means that
connections can be broken just as easily.
That's what will likely happen to you.
Okay.
Make a choice.
Either kill me
or run now while you can.
You'll get yourself killed
trying to save your dad too.
Tell me where the hell he is.
He doesn't matter to you.
Sorry. I…
need the restroom.
[exhales]
[breath trembling]
-[toilet flushing]
-[gasps]
[footsteps]
[door slides open]
[footsteps approach]
[water splashing]
[tape scraping]
[metal scrapes]
[indistinct clattering]
[water sloshing]
[menacing music playing]
Papa!
[Jun-yeong] Welcome.
Let my father go!
Just put that down first.
Do it.
[clatters]
[Na-mi] Papa…
Now stop freaking out and tie yourself up.
[tape scraping]
Now turn around.
Sit and put your hands behind your back.
Now!
-[father grunts]
-[sobbing]
[sobbing] Stop it! Stop it!
-[water running]
-[muffled grunting]
[Na-mi] Okay… Okay…
[water stops running]
[tape scraping]
I gave you many chances.
All of this was your call.
[Na-mi] Papa…
[muffled groaning]
Papa.
I'm sorry.
-[groaning continues]
-Papa?
Hey. Pa.
Don't worry now.
Please be patient. Papa. all right?
[Jun-yeong] How nice.
You should have been
taking better care of him.
I did everything you said.
Keep your end of the deal.
Well. of course.
A promise must be kept always.
[phone clicks]
Though. Na-mi.
no text messages
were sent to your dad by anyone.
I'm keeping my promise.
[Na-mi] What?
[screaming]
-No. please! Dad! No!
-[muffled groaning]
[Na-mi wailing] Dad! No!
[wailing] Please!
You goddamn cocksucker!
I'm gonna kill you. you bastard!
I'm gonna end your life.
you worthless son of a bitch!
[Na-mi screaming]
[sobbing] Oh. God…
[wailing]
[muffled groaning]
[crying] I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'll do everything you want. I promise!
Let him go. Please. no.
Please don't.
[Jun-yeong grunts]
I'm begging you.
Please just let my dad go.
You'll do anything. right?
Please! Yes! Really. I will do anything!
[tape scraping]
You murder him then.
[menacing music playing]
[Na-mi whimpering]
[dark music playing]
[dark music continues]
[menacing music playing]
[camera clicks]
[menacing music fading]
SET AS WALLPAPER
[clatters]
NO TEXTS. ONLY CALLS!
[dramatic music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[suspenseful music building]
[Jeong-ho] Drop it!
Drop it now. you piece of shit!
Oh. shit. It's that jerk-off from earlier.
Who the hell are you? Huh?
Where's Lee Na-mi?
Hey. Father.
[Jeong-ho] What? You crazy bastard!
[Jun-yeong grunts]
[body thuds]
[groaning]
-[blows landing]
-[groaning continues]
[groaning weakly]
[Ji-man] Jun-yeong's not dead!
Where is he?
[Jun-yeong] Dad…
Dad. I'm Jun-yeong!
[pleading] It's me!
I'm your son. Dad. Jun-yeong!
[angrily] I'm this way now…
all because of you!
[sobbing] Please stop hitting me.
It hurts so much!
Dad…
I really fooled you. huh?
Jesus. that moron
couldn't kill anyone. idiot.
[laughs]
[brooding music playing]
[Jun-yeong groans]
[brooding music continues]
[sighs weakly]
Where is Jun-yeong?
0. WOO JUN-YEONG
FAMILY. WOO JI-MAN
POCHEON POLICE STATION
BLAMES HIM FOR HIS MOM'S ILLNESS…
FORCEFUL. CONDESCENDING. SELF-CENTERED
SHALL I LIVE AS WOO JUN-YEONG?
LEAVE SUPPLEMENTS AS TRACES OF JUN-YEONG
TURN HIM INTO A MURDERER
-[breath trembling]
-[phone chimes]
[laughing weakly]
[gags]
Found him.
[somber music playing]
Sorry.
I apologize.
I'll go to prison.
[Jun-yeong faintly] I'll take
legal responsibility for all of this!
I said I'm sorry.
So just…
[laughs weakly] Put the gun down.
you can't…
pull the trigger.
[dramatic music playing]
[mouths] What?
[dramatic music building]
[breath trembling]
[sighs]
[dramatic music continues]
[exhales in disbelief]
[gasps]
[gun fires twice]
[Jun-yeong groans weakly]
[indistinct wheezing]
[hopeful music playing]
[father weakly] Na-mi.…
[Na-mi gasps]
[father] Na-mi.
[wails]
-[Na-mi sobbing]
-[father exclaims]
[somber music playing]
[sirens wailing faintly]
[phones chiming]
[somber music continues]
[phone vibrating]
DROP-DEAD GORGEOUS
WHERE ARE YOU? LET'S MEET UP AND TALK
[breathing regularly]
-[sirens blaring]
-[somber music continues]
[reporter 1] All the victim did
was drop her smartphone.
[reporter 2] Anonymous victim
became the target of a serial killer.
[reporter 1] Police speculate the culprit
to be someone not registered.
[reporter 2] They have announced
they will focus on identifying who he is.
[reporter 3] In an age where
the smartphone has become a necessity.
this could happen to any one of us…
I FOUND KIRKE'S COFFEE SHOP
SHE'S REALLY HERE
REALLY? WHERE IS IT?
WHAT DOES SHE LOOK LIKE?
I SHOULD GO CHECK IT OUT
TELL HER TO STAY STRONG
GO KIRKE!
SEND US A PIC
[dark music playing]
[indistinct chatter on video]
[dark music building]
[camera clicks]
[intriguing music playing]
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today